gameshud.com 2013-08-16

# gameshud.com - Privacy Statement

ARD Media Ltd. (''ARD Media Ltd.'') is committed to preserving the privacy of our users. This Privacy Statement explains which information we collect and how we use it.

The gameshud.com website (''gameshud.com Website'') entitles our users to use the gameshud.com software (the ''Software), both online and after downloading it. To improve our site, we use cookies to save our users' usernames and passwords so that they don't have to re-enter them each time they visit the gameshud.com site. We might also use cookies in the Software to allow us to track from which vendor users access gameshud.com. We also offer our users the option of receiving Help Desk support and our newsletters. As part of the registration process, after downloading the Software, gameshud.com may request the following information: the user's age range, gender, country, zip code, e-mail address and general interests. The purpose of gathering this information is to help gameshud.com provide better service to our users and aggregate information to third parties interested in usage patterns of different demographic groups. gameshud.com may share information about users with business partners, sponsors and other third parties; however, we do so only in the aggregate and never on a personal basis.

ARD Media Ltd. uses this information to contact our users with information related to our Software and services provided through the gameshud.com Website (''Services''), to personalize the Services, to help us understand the use of the Services, and to describe the gameshud.com customer base in general terms to prospective users and the media. When our customers use the Software and Services, we collect and categorize aggregated data, which remains anonymous.

Our users can at any time add, remove or revise e-mail addresses and any other information previously provided to ARD Media Ltd., as well as opting-out of receiving our newsletter by sending an email to info@gameshud.com or by revising the registration form provided with the downloaded software. When publishers sign up to the service of gameshud.com they MUST supply their email address and fill in the registration form. We use this information only in aggregate form to send newsletters about the Software, and in order to send a license code to the publishers for accessing gameshud.com.

Users who fill in the Contact Us page, have to enter their name, email address, and website. We use this information to identify you and understand the problem that you have. We do not send this information to any third party. We use this information solely for the purpose of contacting you.

The gameshud.com Website contains links to other web sites from which the Software can be downloaded. ARD Media Ltd. does not share any information provided by our users with these sites. Additionally, gameshud.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites.

Our Toolbar may contain links to other websites, products and services. This privacy policy only applies to our Sites and our collection and use of your information. The linked websites, product, or services, may govern their privacy policy in a different manner. We encourage you to learn about the privacy practices of those third parties.

From time to time, we may also ask users, optionally, to fill out an online survey to assist us in evaluating the demand for new versions of our Software. These surveys ask visitors for contact information (i.e., name and email address), to facilitate notifying interested customers of new products and services offered by gameshud.com. You are not obligated to give any information in the survey, that you don't want to give, and you are not obligated to fill-in any servey if you do not like to do so.

We also have security measures (such as firewall protection on our servers and PC's) installed to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the user information under our control.

Users should also be aware of the following:

a. The details users elect to post during the registration procedure or thereafter become the property of ARD Media Ltd. upon receipt by gameshud.com;

b. ARD Media Ltd. checks for the following information when using gameshud.com software: your operating system, gameshud.com Software version, browser version, connectivity, and information regarding your use and the configuration of the gameshud.com Software ("Parameters") . Parameters are collected in order to provide you with the Software and Services subject to the provisions of this privacy policy hereof and of the gameshud.com's License Agreement (the "License"), as well as in order to verify that the terms and conditions of the License are not being violated;

c. ARD Media Ltd. gathers information related to our users' use of the our Software (''Usage Patterns'') to better understand how such users, as a group, use the software and the various features thereof, as well as to help gameshud.com tailor offerings to user groups with specific profiles, and to conduct market research. The Parameters and the Usage Patterns may be used in the aggregate for commercial purposes, including without limitation, for marketing, co-registration to other services, promotional activities or any other activity, including, without limitation, the protection of gameshud.com's proprietary and other rights all subject to the provisions herein.

d. ARD Media Ltd. may use a search page for user searches, using this search page is under the privacy terms of the search page, which are found in <http://search.gameshud.com/search/legal/privacy.html>

Questions about this privacy statement should be directed to privacy@gameshud.com
